grabmore.in 2017-12-02

# Privacy Notice

We are completely aware of the point to how important it is to maintain the privacy and security of your personal information. Grabmore.in values the trust of its customers in the first place. When you visit our online store and decide to place an order with us, we would gather information that is required to execute the transaction. Typically, the information would include your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, phone number, debit/credit card information and with this information in hand we also intend to intimate you on any offers or discounts that we propose to provide. The information might also be used for conducting research and analysis to running our business efficiently.

We ensure that all personal details collected are handled with utmost care. We do not store any credit card information of our customers with us. Credit card processing is done by EBS / CCAvenue. In this regard, we'd like to remind you about the following: 

**Use of Information:**

The information that we gather is primarily used to support your interactions with us. We make use of such information to send commercial information such as special offerings, promotional programs etc through e-mails, direct mails, mobile alerts etc. Additionally, we would require them to send you information pertaining to transactions. Further, in order to update you about new products and services which we believe may be of interest to you, we would share your information with third parties.

 **Security:**

We have devised security standards and processes to protect the information provided and further prevent any unauthorized access or disclosure. Technologies such as firewalls and encryption needed to facilitate transmission of sensitive information are employed as per industry standards. In no occasion will the information obtained by us be sold or rented out to third parties. Although third parties such as agents or financial institutions may have access to your personal information, we forbid their right to misuse the same. Nevertheless, we cannot guarantee complete security as the Internet is always prone to certain degree of risk.

Your information under our possession is protected by stringent security measures.

 **Cookies:**

In-order to track user behavior on certain pages and to identify preferences we use data collection devices called cookies. The obtained information is used for internal research and development of the business.

 **Disclosure:**

By law

In compliance with the law of the land, legal procedures or any requests from the government, we would be obliged to share your personal information to third parties.

Mergers and acquisition

Due to strategic reasons, Grabmore may decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize its business. In such case, it becomes necessary to disclose personal information to the prospective buyer or receive information from the seller. As a practice, Grabmore would take appropriate measures to seek protection of the information provided by you.

Finally, Grabmore also gives you the option of accessing or editing the information submitted by you at any point of time. However, please note that the name cannot be changed. You can only re-register to choose a new name.

 **Grievance Officer:**

The contact details of the Grievance Officer are given below in accordance with the Information Technology Act 2000;

Company Name: Grabmore Internet Pvt. Ltd.,  
Address:Old No 45, New No 61,Secretariat Colony, 2nd Street,Kellys,Chennai - 600010,Tamilnadu,India.  
Phone:+91.72999 22929 / 91.98840 12829  
Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a8cfdac1cddec9c6cbcd86c7cecec1cbcddae8cfdac9cac5c7dacd86c1c6)  
Time: Monday through Saturday (9:30AM – 6:30PM)

 **Note:** Grabmore.in reserves the right to change its privacy at any time without notice. It is advised to review this policy periodically to be aware of any changes.
